<Characters>
	<Character>
		<Name>Avalon</Name>
		<Description>
			Although Avalon often hides away in the
			mysterious chambers of grand libraries, he 
			never misses an opportunity to flaunt his 
			opulence and verbosity at cultural 
			gatherings.His charm and cunning have
			enchanted more than one guest at extravagant
			balls. There isn’t a soul who can out-talk
			him - how infuriating thatcan sometimes be!
			Yet, while Avalon may seem excessively 
			talkative and frivolous among people, he 
			cannot tolerate a single distracting whisper
			during his explorations of ancient academic 
			texts.

			Those who truly know Avalon would describe
			himas more enigmatic and contemplative than 
			the jovial socialite with a friend at every 
			corner.Perhaps this is why he dresses so 
			darkly and mysteriously... like a cunning 
			moth flitting among a kaleidoscope of
			vibrant, carefree butterflies.
			
			Avalon isn’t the type to let his true 
			thoughts  slip easily. He is selective with
			his words and remains an enigma even to those
			closest to him. 


		</Description>
	</Character>
	<Character>
		<Name>Tygistae</Name>
		<Description>
			If there’s anyone who extends a helping hand, 
			even to those who might tarnish his own, it’s
			undoubtedly Tygistae. But don’t let his
			innocent face and kind heart fool you—beneath
			that exterior flows the blood of a determined
			warrior. This young man won’t be swayed by the
			advice of those around him. Danger ahead? He’s
			already on his way!

			Tygistae’s fashion sense reflects his free
			spirit. He prefers casual yet cool attire:
			nothing too tight or restrictive for him. 
			Comfort and style go hand in hand; after all,
			what’s the point of looking great if you can’t 
			feel free?

			And what about his strength? Forget angelic 
			auras—Tygistae’s cherished crystals are his 
			true companions. These symbols of resilience
			and quiet power are carried with ease and 
			pride. Every step he takes is grounded in his 
			belief that his  strength comes from within, 
			not from the surface appearance others may 
			expect. He knows that the real power lies in
			how one carries themselves, unyielding in
			spirit even when the world tries to push them 
			down.
		</Description>
	</Character>
	<Character>
		<Name>Inerys</Name>
		<Description>
			A breath as delicate as a blooming flower,
			lips that echo the songs of desperate 
			lovers… Oh, forgive me, I’ve gotten carried
			away.This enchanting beauty may possess the 
			charm of a flower, but her taste is  
			sharper than any thorn. Even if you
			manage to promise her the moon, she’ll 
			decide at the last moment that it was the
			stars she wanted all along.

			Inerys values one thing above all else:
			herself. Much like a rare flower that 
			thrives in solitude, she holds her tastes
			in the highest regard, whether it’s her
			fashion sense or  the company she keeps.
			She mocks those who admire with shallow 
			intentions.

			And what if you somehow manage to win her 
			over?  Should you accomplish the 
			near-impossible, she might pull you out
			of any trouble with a grace and
			elegance so effortless you’d think her
			a fairy. But don’t expect her to make
			it easy—Inerys always keeps things 
			on her terms. 
			
		</Description>
	</Character>
	<Character>
		<Name>Lorainael</Name>
		<Description>
			To bear the weight of the entire world on 
			one’s shoulders is no easy burden. Yet,
			escaping such a heavy fate often proves
			even harder. But Lo'rainael is no coward, 
			she will always choose the harder task, the 
			path fraught with shadows and doubt.What
			is life without the freedom to carve your
			own way?

			But how does one achieve their goals when
			the world’s expectations weigh so heavily?
			For Lo'rainael, the answer lies in 
			blendingin. She moves with her surroundings, 
			like rain that vanishes into the tears of 
			oceans, slipping through unnoticed,
			adapting to the  pallor of her world. 
			Where there is steam, she is its shade; 
			where there is storm, she is its eye...
			
			Speaking to her is simple—her demeanor is 
			unassuming, her words thoughtful—but
			recalling  her afterward is a challenge, 
			as if she were a dream fading with the
			morning mist. Who even is she? Someone 
			who holds sacred her own ambitions,
			honors great promises, and values her ways
			above all.
			
		</Description>
	</Character>
</Characters>